export const questions = {
    "Category 1": [
      { question: "Question 1-1", answer: "Answer 1-1" },
      { question: "Question 1-2", answer: "Answer 1-2" },
      { question: "Question 1-3", answer: "Answer 1-3" },
    ],
    "Category 2": [
      { question: "Question 2-1", answer: "Answer 2-1" },
      { question: "Question 2-2", answer: "Answer 2-2" },
      { question: "Question 2-3", answer: "Answer 2-3" },
    ],
    "Category 3": [
      { question: "Question 3-1", answer: "Answer 3-1" },
      { question: "Question 3-2", answer: "Answer 3-2" },
      { question: "Question 3-3", answer: "Answer 3-3" },
    ],
    "Category 4": [
      { question: "Question 4-1", answer: "Answer 4-1" },
      { question: "Question 4-2", answer: "Answer 4-2" },
      { question: "Question 4-3", answer: "Answer 4-3" },
    ],
    "Category 5": [
      { question: "Question 5-1", answer: "Answer 5-1" },
      { question: "Question 5-2", answer: "Answer 5-2" },
      { question: "Question 5-3", answer: "Answer 5-3" },
    ],
    "Category 6": [
      { question: "Question 6-1", answer: "Answer 6-1" },
      { question: "Question 6-2", answer: "Answer 6-2" },
      { question: "Question 6-3", answer: "Answer 6-3" },
    ],
  };